Hello!

My name is Jayden Szekely, I am an audacious, multi-disciplined creative with experience in graphic design, web / UI design, as well as video editing & design. I see design as more than text, images and colour, I see design as the best opportunity to tell a story to the world. I look forward to having the opportunity to talking with you, to see how I can be a part of writing the next chapter in your story.

I am an outgoing, specialty coffee-loving, pun-cracking, creative located in Whangarei, New Zealand. I enjoy spending my spare-time listening to a mixture of jazz and indie music, while learning something new. I invite you to browse my CV and view my online portfolio.

Get in touch

Phone (+64) 021 122 2857

Email hello@jaydenszekely.com

Portfolio www.jaydenszekely.com



To Whom it May Concern

I have the required skill set and design ability accompanied with an eye for detail to meet the requirements of your advertised position. I believe this makes me a strong candidate for your vacancy.

Working as a freelance web & graphic designer for the previous four years, has provided me with a solid foundation in a variety of different areas and disciplines.

In 2018 I graduated from Media Design School with a New Zealand Certificate in Arts and Design, as well as a New Zealand Certificate in Digital Media and Design. These qualifications strengthened my existing understanding and skillset in the creative field.

I invite you to browse my online portfolio 'www.jaydenszekely.com'. My portfolio includes a curated selection of previous design projects. When you're viewing my portfolio, I hope you can visualise how my creative ability can be an asset to your company. Upon request I have other samples of creative projects that I can share with you.

Thank you for considering my application. Please find on the following two pages a copy of my CV.

I look forward to talking with you soon!

Warm regards,

Jayden Szekely



Personal Qualities

Loyal, self motivated, goal driven, enthusiastic, creative, problem solver, quick learner, out-of-the-box thinker, excellent communicator, leader, and most importantly - passionate about great (whilst functional) design.

Qualifications & Awards

New Zealand Certificate in Arts and Design New Zealand Certificate in Digital Media Honours from the Awwwards & Nomination from CSS Nectar

Experience

I have experience working with a range of clients and in-house positions for independent ventures, small companies and large non-profit organisations and I am now looking for my next challenge.

Freelance Creative Volunteer Designer

2015 to Current ARISE Church 2016 to Jan 2019

Intern Designer Marketing Manager

ARISE Church The Outdoor Room Company
Feb 2019 to June 2019 May 2019 to Current (Part Time)



UI / UX | Visual Design

Using software, including Adobe XD and Sketch, I have created well thought out solutions to design problems for over four years. I create with purpose, from discussions through wireframing, to the final design. The user is my number one focus.

Front-end Development

Over the last six years, I have developed many websites using modern frameworks and languages including ReactJS, Sass/Scss, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery and minimal exposure with Ruby on Rails. I currently use Netlify as my main CMS however I have experience with Wordpress also.

Graphic Design

I have been involved with a variety of projects for a broad range of mediums. I am profficient with the entire Adobe Creative Suite including Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign and After Effects.

Photo | Video

Photo and video has always been a passion. I have had the privelege of working on a variety of projects. These projects have allowed me to strengthen my skills in Adobe After Effects, Premiere Pro and Lightroom for editing photographs.

Other Skills

Social Media Management, SEO, Google Adwords, GitHub, Audio Production and Project Management.

